{
    "subject": "resource/Misrata_District",
    "predicate": "ontology/capital",
    "object": "resource/Misrata",
    "human_readable": "The capital of Misrata District is Misrata.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9885353446006775,
            "question": "Is Misrata the capital of Misrata District?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9845494031906128,
            "question": "What is the capital of Misrata District?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9049983620643616,
            "question": "What is the main city within the Misrata District?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9019001126289368,
            "question": "What is the name of the Libyan district with Misrata as its capital?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8751318454742432,
            "question": "Is there a city in Libya called Misrata that serves as a district capital?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8162104487419128,
            "question": "Where is Misrata located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7598772048950195,
            "question": "Which city holds administrative power over the Misrata District?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7522551417350769,
            "question": "If you were visiting the Misrata District, what city would you go to for government services?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1635598987340927,
            "question": "Can you name a Libyan city that also functions as a district's capital?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.12701912224292755,
            "question": "Name a city in Libya that serves as a district capital."
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The capital of Misrata District is Misrata.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9103_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name a Libyan city that also functions as a district's capital?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9103_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If you were visiting the Misrata District, what city would you go to for government services?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9103_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which city holds administrative power over the Misrata District?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9103_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9103_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9103_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9103_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9103_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9103_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9103_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9103_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9103_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9103_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9103_78.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After evaluating the context information, I can confirm that:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents support the triple \"The capital of Misrata District is Misrata.\" as it consistently mentions that Misrata is both a city and the capital city of the Misrata District."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents state that \"Misrata is the capital city of the Misrata District,\" which supports the query stating that the capital of Misrata District is Misrata."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}